Do you know why you don't get math?
FINAL EXAM
IN 16 DAYS
Because you don't know the logic.
You memorize everything
without knowing the reason behind it.
Oh Beom-seok.
Class is almost over.
I'm sorry.
Anyway,
everyone should think hard
about why I told you this today.
Class president.
Attention. Bow.
Thank you.
Beom-seok.
Did you go drinking?
Beom-seok!
You good?
Your head killing you?
Yeah, and my guts aren't too good either.
Hey.
I can't remember how it ended.
You were fucking funny last night.
And that punk Yong-jin
definitely banged that girl.
Seriously?
Yeah! Don't you remember?
You paid for the motel.
- I paid for it?
- Yeah!
- Dude!
- He really doesn't remember.
Let's go for a smoke.
Thanks for the drinks.
Seriously, last night was really fun.
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
What group are we in?
Group six.
The seat at the end is mine.
Oh Beom didn't come to school yet?
- He came.
- He did?
When?
Beom-seok, that girl couldn't keep
her hands off your legs last night!
Man, I was wondering.
- About what?
- Hey.
You rapped in English at karaoke.
It was fucking wild.
You got some pent-up rage or what?
Let's go again.
Just us without Yong-jin.
Yeah. Yong-jin totally stole
that girl from you.
Let's have a chat.
What is this?
What's what?
Why did you ignore my calls?
I didn't know you called.
What's with them?
Why are you suddenly friends
with Jeong-chan and Tae-hun?
It's none of your business.
You, Su-ho, and I should talk.
I have nothing to say.
That bastard Su-ho looked down on me
from the start.
The bastard never saw me as a friend.
I was just a lackey to him.
You're talking behind my back now?
So what?
Drink!
Great job!
What's up?
Beom-seok.
Long time no see.
Yeah, it's been a while.
- Come here.
- Sit here, Beom-seok.
This is Oh Beom-seok,
a friend from my old school.
Assemblyman Oh Jin-won's son.
Who's that?
You know, that National Assembly guy.
Oh, really?
Awesome!
Meet Seo-hyeon, Ji-an, and Su-a.
Friends from my new school.
And Kang Woo-yeong.
A future UFC fighter and my friend.
You know Physical Therapist Woo-yeong?
What physical therapy?
Look it up later.
It's an online channel where he spars
with dumbass posers.
It's fucking funny.
Hey, man.
Yeah, nice to meet you.
Oh, right.
I heard you split from those fuckers,
Si-eun and Su-ho.
- Yes.
- What happened?
You guys were tight.
Su-ho thinks he's the fucking king.
Yeah, that guy fucking sucks.
He looks down on everyone.
I need to beat the hell
out of that fucker someday.
Anyway,
sorry about before.
Let's drink!
Drink!
- Drink up!
- Cheers!
Fuck, I want to transfer too.
Isn't he your type?
Some experts…
What did they estimate?
DAESUNG ACADEMY
Hey, Si-eun!
What is it?
It's Friday!
Let's ride all night.
Get on.
It's cute.
Apartment 901.
Think of it as training. Take the stairs.
Are you making me work?
It's not like that.
I'm just helping you get stronger.
I'll be back soon.
Cheers!
Killer, right?
How is Yeong-i's new job going?
Yeah, she's actually quite smart,
and she's friendly with people.
I think that…
Jeong-chan and Tae-hun
are taking advantage of Beom-seok.
And?
I think he's buying them
shoes and clothes.
He pays for all their drinks too.
He always reeks of booze.
Maybe Oh Beom's using them.
It's just
he wanted that from the start.
That's why he latched on to us.
He wanted to be popular.
He thought
we made him look like a big shot.
Do you really think so?
Had a fun weekend?
Yeong-bin brought some hotties.
Fucking traitors!
- I'll go out with one.
- For real?
Stop daydreaming, you fucking moron!
It's true love.
Her eyes sparkled when she looked at me.
'Cause you look old for high school!
You look like a little kid.
- Want to take this outside?
- Bring it on.
Seo-hyeon messaged me.
- No way, man.
- Seo-hyeon?
- Knock it off!
- Why would she?
She slid into my DMs.
She messaged me first and asked me out.
- For real?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, right.
- Can we come meet her?
- What about me?
- Not this guy.
No way!
- Ask her to bring Su-a.
- What about us?
I'll ask her.
- Ji-an! No, not Ji-an.
- What about us?
- Ask Su-a for me.
- Three is enough.
- And us too?
- Her pics are hot!
- Message her!
- Nah, later.
Seriously?
Are you coming over here now?
Fine!
- Beom-seok.
- I'm fed up!
What?
- Su-a, again?
- Yeah.
Of course! Please message her.
Nice seat, isn't it?
It's awesome.
The rent is 100 million won.
Buy me something big.
- I'll treat you this weekend.
- Bet!
But not Tae-hun.
I won't go then.
Come on. We need you for the ugly girl.
Stop using Beom-seok.
What?
Don't take advantage of him.
What is this bullshit?
School is so scary now.
You buy shoes and drink alcohol
using Beom-seok's cash.
Fuck, you say that
like we're the bad guys.
Hey.
If he wants to pay, what's the problem?
I've said my piece.
Let's go eat.
Don't worry about Beom-seok.
What?
You've done enough. You tried.
I think Beom-seok…
is just lonely.
I'm not sure.
Just a feeling.
What's for lunch?
Shit, perilla leaves?
Who wants to feed them to me?
Hey!
What are you doing?
There's a line.
Get in line.
I don't get it.
Get in line, Beom-seok.
I don't want to.
Enough.
Goddamn it.
Let's go.
Are you fucking serious?
Fucking hell! That asshole has no respect.
Hey.
Do you know anyone who can waste him?
- What?
- I can pay.
Can anyone kill that bastard?
Oh fuck!
- What?
- Woo-yeong.
I watched some of his videos
on his channel.
He's fucking good.
PHYSICAL THERAPIST WOO-YEONG
- That's it.
- Fuck, this could work.
He could do it.
He throws good punches.
How much can you pay?
Is a million won enough?
When?
This Saturday.
Su-ho's birthday.
All right.
I'll live stream it. Unedited.
- Where are you going?
- The gym.
That's diligence.
Hold on.
Didn't Ahn Su-ho waste him
a while back in a competition?
Hey, that was a long time ago.
Su-ho retired. Woo-yeong still fights.
- No problem.
- Hey.
Make him fight with a handicap
if you're so worried.
Am I wrong?
Hey, isn't this it?
I think this is it. Let me see.
Here we go. Fuck.
It's hard to cut!
I hope that's the one.
Fuck, couldn't this really kill him?
Don't know. Don't care.
Shit!
Look out!
What was that?
Hey, are you all right?
- Please call an ambulance.
- I'm calling now.
Can you move?
Hey.
Let's go before we get screwed.
Hey, Beom-seok!
Hurry up!
- I'm okay.
- Are you sure?
I'm all right.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
Now, what did I tell you
about Song of the Green Mountain?
You just got here?
I'm sorry.
Eyes up here!
I'll go over it one last time.
A trimeter song with stanzas and a chorus.
This song demonstrates
the most basic elements
of the Goryeo period…
What happened?
It's no big deal.
Hey.
Don't look at me.
You make me sick.
Get lost.
What was that?
Nothing.
Shit, that fucking scared me.
Do you think he knows it was us?
How could he?
I hope not. I mean, there's no way.
Is his birthday the day after tomorrow?
It's done!
If Su-ho hadn't gotten hurt,
we would've gone to Yangyang.
Take pictures.
Take nice ones.
People will think it's your birthday.
Hurry up.
Still no answer?
No.
Maybe he blocked you.
The number you have called
cannot be reached…
What's your problem?
Nothing.
Hey.
He won't be here for 30 minutes.
Why are you cooking seaweed soup already?
I heard it tastes better
if you cook it longer.
Says who?
MY BUDDY SI-EUN, LOOK HERE
BEOM-SEOK: ARE YOU AT THE PARTY ROOM?
ARE YOU AT THE PARTY ROOM?
I'M NEARBY. CAN I SEE YOU A MINUTE?
Hey.
Didn't you cut ties with Beom-seok?
Su-ho said that?
IT'S SU-HO'S BIRTHDAY TODAY
No, he didn't.
Why are you suddenly asking about him?
DON'T TELL SI-EUN OR SU-HO
COME OUT FOR A MINUTE
SO I CAN GIVE YOU HIS PRESENT
Oh? It's nothing.
I'm going to the shop.
It's been a while.
How's it going?
Good, I guess.
How about you?
Fine.
Sorry about before.
I caused problems by answering your phone.
Si-eun was so worried about you.
Su-ho will be here soon.
So come to the party with me.
I'll help you guys make up.
Hey.
First of all,
you didn't cause problems.
And what can you do?
And why would we make up?
Is he for real?
What is this?
If you go that way…
Don't play so methodically. Look.
This isn't studying. It's a game.
Okay, my turn.
Hey, is Yeong-i crawling or something?
Why's it taking so long? I'm starving.
We can have the cake later.
Let's just eat first.
You seriously…
had a great idea. I mean it.
I like it.
- I'll try calling Yeong-i.
- Okay.
The number you called cannot be reached.
Leave a message after the beep.
Did you know
reheated leftover pizza is hella tasty?
Get ready.
It'll blow your mind.
BEOM-SEOK
18-3 BAMGOGAE-RO, GANGNAM, SEOUL
STOP IGNORING MY CALLS AND GET OVER HERE
Don't look at me. You make me sick.
Hey, now Yeong-i isn't a problem.
Hey. Didn't you cut ties with Beom-seok?
I'm going to the shop.
Hurry up and take a seat.
This smells great. Holy shit.
YOUR BIRTHDAY PRESENT LOL
Hell yeah, check out this cheese.
So good.
Start without me.
Okay.
I also want chicken, but I'll resist.
You know what I mean?
ON MY WAY. WAIT FOR ME
DELETE 6 MESSAGES
BEOM-SEOK IS BLOCKED
SLIDE TO POWER OFF
- I'm going to the shop.
- Right now?
Hey.
Hurry up.
I can't wait more than five minutes.
Be right back.
Go ahead and eat.
Damn, I need a smoke.
Su-ho wouldn't answer my calls,
but he's coming now
after seeing your picture.
Hey. Shut up.
Your breath smells like shit.
Hey.
I'm curious.
Are you dating Su-ho?
Fuck, what's this bullshit?
I mean, that's how relationships work.
There's always give and take.
Su-ho lets you stay at his house.
He gets you a job.
So what did you give him in return?
Don't be ridiculous.
The Battle of Thermopylae.
To defeat a much larger army,
Sparta fought them in a narrow pass.
To fight against many opponents,
you need to utilize the terrain.
What's this?
Si-eun!
Fuck, it's been a while, Yeon Si-eun.
Why are you here? Where's Su-ho?
It's fucking good to see you.
Let's go.
Fuck!
What are you doing? Grab him!
What's going on? Where's Ahn Su-ho?
God!
You go first!
I'll get the police!
Son of a bitch!
Hurry up!
Get them!
Please come right away.
They're going to fuck us up!
- Hey!
- Yes, they're coming after me!
Where are you going?
Yeon Si-eun!
Son of a bitch!
You fucker.
That hurts!
Hey. Wait a minute.
Hey, hold on.
Wait a minute!
Hell yeah!
Who are you?
The Foul King?
Are you Yeong-bin's friend?
That won't help you.
You're using a tool, you son of a bitch?
Fucking coward.
Enough.
Just let him go.
- What?
- Si-eun isn't involved.
I said let him go.
I only need Su-ho.
That's your business.
This is mine.
Fuck! I told you to stop.
You crazy fucker.
Hey.
What?
We're all here to help you, asshole.
So he's your friend.
What about us?
Didn't I tell you
to know your place?
You fucker.
Hit that fucker more!
You son of a bitch.
You fucking dog!
Just pound him.
Hey, Beom-seok.
Let's reschedule the Ahn Su-ho fight.
I've already promoted it
a lot on my channel.
Transfer the money for today, okay?
I got you one punk.
Fuck!
Fuck, did you think we were pushovers?
My jaw still hurts.
My jaw! You son of a bitch.
Hit him more. Fuck.
Hey!
The bitch called the cops!
Hurry up!
Fuck! Let's go!
Let's get out of here!
Hey.
You thought you won, didn't you?
Hey, Yeon Si-eun.
Si-eun.
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS SHOWN
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL
Subtitle translation by: James Webb